madefreshly.com 2014-02-16

# MADEFRESHLY | Privacy

MadeFreshly collects email addresses of people who send us email. Such information may contain personal data about you including your address, phone numbers, PayPal account etc. We are not allowed to disclose such personal information without your written permission. However, certain information collected from you and about you is used within the context of providing the Service. The information we collect is not shared with or sold to others except under the certain circumstances and which your use of the Service is deemed to provide to us a valid consent to disclose the following:  

  1. In order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MadeFreshly's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  2. MadeFreshly does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other companies except to provide products or services you have requested or when we have your permission.
  3. We will transfer information about you if MadeFreshly is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MadeFreshly will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the MadeFreshly web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**What we do with Your Information**  

  1. When you register for MadeFreshly we ask for your name, email address, and billing information.
  2. MadeFreshly uses the information we collect for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.
  3. As part of the buying and selling process on MadeFreshly, you will obtain the email address and/or shipping address of your customers. By entering into our Terms of Service, you agree that, with respect to other users' personal information that you obtain through MadeFreshly or through a Made Freshly-related communication or MadeFreshly-facilitated transaction, MadeFreshly hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for MadeFreshly-related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages. MadeFreshly does not tolerate SPAM. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add the name of someone who has purchased an item from you, to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express consent.

**Security**  

The security of your personal information is important to us. When your customers enter sensitive information, such as credit card number on our registration form, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Disclosure**  

MadeFreshly may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with court orders requiring us to do so or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

**Client Data Storage**

MadeFreshly owns the data storage, databases and all right to the MadeFreshly application however we make no claim to the rights of your data. You retain all rights to your data and we will never contact your clients directly.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. MadeFreshly uses cookies to record current  
session information, our cookies generally last two weeks. You are required to log-in to your MadeFreshly site after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing the content of your account.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make any changes to this policy, customers will be notified by email.
